<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Awesomeness</title>
      <link>/unused/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/unused/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>The James Jansson Team for NSW is planning for a bigger, brighter future for NSW. We&amp;rsquo;re free of vested interests and factional forces. We&amp;rsquo;re focused on delivering results to the people of NSW. We&amp;rsquo;re the candidates for humans.
We&amp;rsquo;re primarily made up of members and volunteers for the Science Party. The Science Party is not registered at the state level, we are running an independent ticket. Read the Federal Science Party policies here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate</title>
      <link>/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/donate/</guid>
      <description>Help the James Jansson Team let the people of NSW know that we&amp;rsquo;re a viable alternative to the extablished parties.  Legal disclaimer:  By making this donation, you are declaring that you are not banned from making donations under NSW law. Individuals who are restricted from donating include owners, directors and close associates of tobacco, liquor, gambling or property development businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>